securitykiss.com 2019-01-12

# SecurityKISS - Free VPN Service

## Privacy Policy

SecurityKISS is committed to protecting your privacy online. Our privacy policy is simple: keep the minimum information about users.

### Logging Policy

We do not monitor, record or store logs for any connection activity, except for the following:
  * Time and duration of the user VPN connection
  * Bandwidth used during the connection
  * User IP address

We use this data only to monitor service usage per user and to generate statistics.

It would be technically unfeasible to maintain log files with details about user activity because of the huge amount of data which is transferred through our servers.

The logs are automatically deleted after 10 days and the only information that is kept for a long time is total usage per billing period (for example 14GB in given month) and SecurityKISS client ID.

### Collecting Personal Information

We do not store any personal information except for: 
  * email address if you enter it on the website
  * user's name and address if we receive them from the payment system

When using the free version of SecurityKISS Tunnel we do not typically have any of this information.   
Upgrading to the premium version can also be completely anonymous if you pay with Bitcoin.

We never collect any financial information like credit card numbers.

On request we can delete all personal information from our service except the email address which we use to contact with the user.

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the data under our control.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will never release any information about you or your account to anyone except law enforcement personnel with the proper documentation and paperwork. We do not and will not monitor user sessions for inappropriate behavior, unless compelled to by law enforcement with proper documentation and paperwork.

We are under Ireland jurisdiction. It has never happened that we disclosed users information to anyone.

### Important note

SecurityKISS is unique with regard to privacy and anonymity because registration is not required to use our service, we are not aware of any other VPN service that does not require registration.   
In the free version we do not even need your email address, go to the website, download the program and connect.  
How can you achieve more anonymity?
